

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- @ aaa@gmail.com
- +48 000 000 000
- www.github.com/mizuris
- in <u>www.linkedin.com/in/piotr-bątor</u>
- **f** www.facebook.com/piotr.bator.33

■ PROFILE

I am freelance frontend developer and graphics designer with over 4 years of experience. I consider myself hard-working and dedicated to my work. For past two years I've been fascinated with frontend technologies and I am willing to learn everyday.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2020 - NOW | Freelance

Building websites and Single Page Applications. Working with modern technologies. Keeping contact with client. Creating mockups and layouts via Figma or Illustrator.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

2017 - NOW | DrukOn

Creating graphic project for clients. Building layouts for websites and creating mockups. Using tools like Affinity Photo, Illustrator or CorelDRAW.

■ EDUCATION

WYŻSZA SZKOŁA BANKOWA

2020 - 2021 | Postgraduate Degree

Frontend developer profile.

UNIWERSYTET KAZIMIERZA WIELKIEGO

2012 - 2015 | Bachelor degree

Administration.

STACK

HTML5 CSS3

JavaScript (Es6+)

TypeScript

ReactJS

Next.js

Node.js

GIT

Illustrator

Figma

SOFT SKILLS

Communication
Problem solving
Organization
Time management
Mulit-tasking
Teamwork

INTERESTS

Sport
Technology
Video games
Automotive